<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Tour</string>
    <string name="category_vizag">Vizag</string>
    <string name="cateory_amaravathi">Amaravathi</string>
    <string name="category_chittor">Chittor</string>
    <string name="category_kurnool">kurnool</string>
    <string name="myTitle">myTitle</string>
    <string name="mySubTitle">mySubTitle</string>
    <string name="myDesc">myDesc</string>
    <string name="myImg">myImg</string>
    <string name="caves_title">Borra Caves</string>
    <string name="caves_subTitle">Araku , Vizag</string>
    <string name="caves_desc">The Borra Caves, also called Borra Guhalu (Borra means hole in Odia language and guhalu means caves in Telugu language), are located on the East Coast of India, in the Ananthagiri hills of the Araku Valley (with hill ranges  elevation varying from 800 to 1,300 m [2,600 to 4,300 ft]) of the Visakhapatnam district in Andhra Pradesh. The caves, one of the largest in the country, at an elevation of about 705 m (2,313 ft), distinctly exhibit a variety of speleothems ranging in size and irregularly shaped stalactites and stalagmites. The caves are basically karstic limestone structures extending to a depth of 80 m (260 ft), and are considered the deepest caves in India</string>
    <string name="beach_title">R.K Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_subTitle">Vizag Coast</string>
    <string name="beach_desc">The beach offers exciting opportunities to surf and when visitors have had their fill of sun, sand and sea, they can explore the poignant Dutch cemeteries located along the beach. The coconut trees bordering the beach just add to the appeal and beauty of the place. The cool ocean breeze, the blue skies, the golden sands and the inviting waves of the sea make a heady mix that is worth experiencing.
</string>
    <string name="ins_title">INS-kansura</string>
    <string name="ins_subtitle">R.K beach Road</string>
    <string name="ins_desc">INS Kursura (S20) was a Kalvari-class diesel-electric submarine of the Indian Navy. She was Indias fifth submarine. Kursura was commissioned on 18 December 1969 and was decommissioned on 27 February 2001 after 31 years of service</string>
    <string name="zoo_title">Indira Gandhi Zoological Park</string>
    <string name="zoo_subtitle">Yendada Nursery, Visakhapatnam</string>
    <string name="zoo_desc">Indira Gandhi Zoological Park is located amidst Kambalakonda Reserve Forest in Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh, India. It is the third largest zoo in the country. The zoological park is named after the former Prime Minister of India, Indira Gandhi.</string>
    <string name="stupa_title">Amaravathi Stupa</string>
    <string name="stupa_subtitle">Amaravathi Road</string>
    <string name="stupa_desc">The Amarāvatī Stupa, popularly known as the great stūpa at Amarāvathī, is a ruined Buddhist monument, probably built in phases between the third century BCE and about 250 CE, at Amaravathi village, Guntur district, Andhra Pradesh, India</string>
    <string name="statue_title">Dhyana Buddha statue</string>
    <string name="statue_subtitle">Amaravathi</string>
    <string name="statue_desc"> This statue was the capital of Satavahanas who ruled from 3rd century BCE to 3rd century CE who are much favor in Buddhism expanded it. The most important historic monument in Amaravathi town is the Mahachaitya. It is protected by the Archaeological Survey of India which maintains a site museum known as old museum</string>
    <string name="museum_title">Archaeological Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_subtitle">Main Road,Amarvathi</string>
    <string name="museum_desc">The Amaravati Archaeological Museum is a museum located in Amaravati, a village in Guntur district of the Indian state of Andhra Pradesh. It is running by Andhra Pradesh tourism. It opens at morning 10:00 and closed at 5:00 pm and Friday holiday</string>
    <string name="tirumala_title">Venkateswara Temple</string>
    <string name="tirumala_subtitle">Tirumala, Tirupathi</string>
    <string name="tirumala_desc">It is the richest temple in the world in terms of donations received and wealth.The temple is visited by about 50,000 to 100,000 pilgrims daily (30 to 40 million people annually on average), while on special occasions and festivals, like the annual Brahmotsavam, the number of pilgrims shoots up to 500,000, making it the most-visited holy place in the world. In 2016, it was reported that 27.3 million pilgrims visited the temple</string>
    <string name="tirumalaPark_title">Sri Venkateswara Zoo Park</string>
    <string name="tirumlaPark_subtitle">SV Zoo Road, Tirupati</string>
    <string name="tirumalaPark_desc">Big zoo featuring an array of exotic animals, including white tigers, plus a lion safari.</string>
    <string name="fort_title">Chandragiri Fort</string>
    <string name="fort_subtitle">Chandragiri Fort Road, Chandragiri</string>
    <string name="fort_desc">Chandragiri Fort is a historical fort, built in the 11th century located in Chandragiri, Tirupati in Andhra Pradesh, India. Tough mostly associated with Vijayanagara Kings it was built much earlier in 11th century by Yadava Naidu kings</string>
    <string name="kurnoolcaves_title">Belum Caves</string>
    <string name="kurnoolcaves_subtitle">Kolimigundla , Kurnool</string>
    <string name="kurnoolcaves_desc">The Belum Caves is the largest and longest cave system open to the public on the Indian subcontinent, known for its speleothems, such as stalactite and stalagmite formations</string>
    <string name="kurnooltemple_title">Mallikarjuna Jyotirlinga Temple</string>
    <string name="kurnooltemple_subtitle">Srisailam ,Kurnool</string>
    <string name="kurnooltemple_desc">Sri Bhramaramba Mallikarjuna Temple is a Hindu temple dedicated to the deities Shiva and Parvati, located at Srisailam in Indian state of Andhra Pradesh. It is significant to the Hindu sects of both Shaivam and Shaktam as this temple is referred to as one of the twelve Jyothirlingas of Lord Shiva and as one of the eighhteen Shakti Peethas of goddess Parvati. Shiva is worshiped as Mallikarjuna, and is represented by the lingam. His consort Parvati is depicted as Brahmaramba. It is the only temple in India which is revered as both Jyotirlinga and Shaktipeeth.</string>
    <string name="rock_titile">Orvakal Rock Garden</string>
    <string name="rock_subtitle">chittoor road, Kurnool</string>
    <string name="rock_desc">Orvakal Rock Garden, or Oravakallu Rock Garden, is the 1000 acre Sculpture Garden park with ancient cave and igneous rock formations between pools of water.</string>
    <string name="sample_text">Sample Text</string>
    <string name="content_desc_item_img">Limited height image for list of items</string>
    <string name="content_desc_place_img">Full height for individual view (more information on item)</string>
    <string name="string_i_need">STRING_I_NEED</string>
    <string name="place_info">Information</string>
</resources>
